Guide to the Gay Men's Health Crisis records
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series II. Executive Director, 1982-1996; 57.5 boxes
  - II. D. Jeff Richardson, 1984, 1990-1996; 6.5 boxes
    Jeff Richardson was Executive Director of GMHC from 1993 to 1995. Richardson created the Department of Treatment Education and Advocacy in 1994 which expanded GMHC's advocacy for improved HIV/AIDS drug research and augmented delivery of treatment education to GMHC's clients. He also oversaw the creation of GMHC's Tuberculosis Education and Treatment Support Program during a severe outbreak of the disease in New York City.
    This subseries contains correspondence, memoranda, minutes, reports, and other material from Jeff Richardson's tenure as Executive Director.
    - Administrative Highlights
      - 1993-1994 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - 1995 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Action Committee, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Action Council, 1993-1995 (Box 73, Folder 3-7)
    - AIDS and Adolescents Network of New York, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - AIDS and Prisons, 1990-1991 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - AIDS Awareness Day, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Community Services Program, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - AIDS Institute
      - General, 1993-1994 (Box 74, Folder 1-3)
      - Community Follow-up Program, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Monthly Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 74, Folder 5-7)
      - Tuberculosis Training Proposal, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - AIDS Prevention, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Prevention and Training Department, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AMFAR), 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Bailey, Dan, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - The Balm in Gilead, Inc., 1994 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Bathhouses and sex clubs, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Big 6 Executive Directors, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Black Gay and Lesbian Leadership Forum, 1993-1994 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Black History Month, 1993-1995 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors Contact Sheet, 1993-1995 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Board of Education, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Broadway Cares, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Budget (Box 75, Folder 13-14)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 75, Folder 13-14)
      - 1996 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Burroughs Wellcome Co., 1993-1995 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - CBO Membership Associate, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Child Life News, 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Children and AIDS, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - City Hall Conferences, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Clarion Newsletter, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Clarion Update, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Client Advocacy Policy and Procedure Manual, 1994? (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Client Advocacy Program Review, 1993-1994 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Client complaints, 1994 (Box 406, Folder 3)
    - Client programs, 1993-1994 (Box 76, Folder 9-10)
    - Clinical Services Department, 1993-1994 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Communications Department, 1993-1994 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Cuomo, Mario, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Deaf AIDS Project (DAP), 1990-1991, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Democratic County Committee of New York County, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Department of Health, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Development
      - General, 1993-1994 (Box 76, Folder 18)
      - Corporate and Government Funding, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 19)
      - Food Fund, 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 20)
      - Major Gifts and Donors, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 21)
      - Special Events, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Development Department
      - General, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Job Descriptions, 1992-1993 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Dinkins, David N., 1993 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Educational Committee Meetings, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Education Department
      - Substance Use Counseling and Education (SUCE), 1994 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Treatment Education and Advocacy, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Evaluation Research, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Finance Committee, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Finance Department, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Financial Statements, 1993-1994 (Box 77, Folder 12-13)
    - Healthcare Reform, 1993-1994 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - HIV in the Workplace, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Hotline, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - House of Latex Project, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Housing Advocacy and Homeless Prevention, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Intake and Client Information Systems, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Legal Services, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Lesbian AIDS Project, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Letter Style, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Letters of Agreement, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Letters of Support to Other Organizations, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Management Consultant, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Management Team minutes, 1993-1995 (Box 78, Folder 12-13)
    - Marcus, Ilene, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Medical and Health Research Association of New York City (MHRA), 1993-1995 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Memoranda, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Mitchell, Maria, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Monthly Administrative Highlights, 1994-1996 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Morning Party, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - New York Post, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Organizational Capability Statement, 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Organizational Chart, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Policies and Procedures Manual, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Program Audits and Reviews, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Staff Memoranda, 1994-1995 (Box 79, Folder 6-7)
    - Strategic Plan for GMHC, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Tour of GMHC, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Treatment Issues, 1993-1994 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Policy and Procedures Manual, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Series III. Client Programs, 1988-1998; 13.5 boxes
  The Client Programs department oversaw the various services provided by GMHC to help clients adapt to and live life with HIV/AIDS. The name of this department changed a number of times and included Program Operations and Program Management. The department was responsible for creating new programs, managing existing programs, and maintaining funding for both.
  The department administered the following units:
  Client Services Client Advocacy Education Department Legal Services Office of the Ombudsman Volunteer Office
  Each of these units had a department head who reported to the Deputy Executive Director for Client Programs.
  The records of Client Services, the Education Department, Legal Services, and the Office of the Ombudsman are not part of this series but are available respectively in Series IV, VII, IX and X of the collection. The records of the Client Advocacy department and the Volunteer Office were not transferred from GMHC, although small amounts of materials related to these departments may be found throughout the collection.
  The series contains reports, memoranda, and correspondence from the Client Programs department. Included here are statistics and summary reports on existing programs and proposals for new programs. The series is divided into three subseries and contains the Administrative Files of the department, records of the Deaf AIDS Project, and records of the Tuberculosis Education and Treatment Support Program.
  - III. A. Administrative Files, 1988-1998; 10.5 boxes
    This series contains reports, memoranda, notes, and correspondence produced by the Client Programs department. Included are Monthly Program Reports which contain statistics and summaries of programs for the AIDS Institute and the Medical and Health Research Association of New York City. There are also proposals for the department's Immigrants with HIV-Related Illness Project and the Food Services Proposal, both funded by the first Ryan White CARE Act.
    The Immigrants with HIV-Related Illness Project was created to provide legal services for immigrants in New York City with HIV-related illness. The project sought to obtain government benefits for immigrants and help with housing, discrimination, and personal affairs planning such as wills and medical directives. The Food Services Program was created in 1986 by the Recreation Department of Client Programs to provide meals five days a week to clients who were homeless, living in shelters, and/or were eligible for Medicare and/or Medicaid. The food program provided a social and safe atmosphere for clients, encouraging them to participate in the menu creation and the preparation of meals. The 1991 Proposal sought to expand the services by 15,600 more meals per week.
    - Annual Expenditures Reports, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Anonymous Applicant Survey, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Backup, 1989-1992 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Bridges
      - Budget Modification, 1992-1993 (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - Hospital Discharge Contract, 1993-1994 (Box 80, Folder 10-11)
      - Project Proposal, 1991-1992 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - The Bronx Technical Assistance Project Proposal, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Budget
      - Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Modifications, 1992-1995 (Box 81, Folder 4-5)
    - Case Management, 1992-1994 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - City Council, Testimony to, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Client Advocacy
      - General, 1992-1993 (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Budget Modifications, 1992-1993 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Communications Department Activities, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Community Follow-up Program Quarterly Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Community Service Provider (CSP)
      - Budget Modifications, 1994-1995 (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - Contract, 1994-1995 (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - Monthly Reports, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 1-2)
    - Comprehensive Medicaid Case Management (CMCM)
      - Application for Continuation, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 3-4)
      - Budget Modification, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Continued Funding Application (CFA), 1991-1995 (Box 82, Folder 6-8)
    - Contract, 1992-1994 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Contract Negotiations, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Department of Health Client Incentive Distribution Form, 1996-1997 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Executed Contracts
      - Case Management, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - Client Advocacy, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - Group Support Services, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Hot Meals, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Mental Health, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Nutrition, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Technical Assistance, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1995 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Final Expenditure Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Food Services Proposal, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Funding Application Form, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Funding Proposals, 1991-1992 (Box 84, Folder 4-5)
    - Group Services Budget Modification, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - HIV Counseling Testing Proposal, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - HIV Health Care Services
      - Back Up, 1989-1992 (Box 84, Folder 8)
      - Mental Health Proposal, 1991-1992 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - HIV Training Initiatives for Health and Human Services Providers, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Hot Meals, 1992-1994 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Human Resources Contract, 1994-1995 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - The Immigrants with HIV-Related Illness Project, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Intensive Case Management Services Proposal, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Legal Services Contract, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Lesbian AIDS Project Proposal, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Lesbian and Gay Young Adult Program, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Lesbian Outreach Project, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Lesbian Support Services Proposal, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Linkages, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Memoranda, 1991-1996 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Mental health, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Mental health budget modifications, 1993-1994 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Mental health Linkage Program Proposal, 1991-1994 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Monthly Program Reports
      - Case Management, 1992-1995 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Client Advocacy, 1992-1993 (Box 86, Folder 3-4)
      - Community Service Program, 1994-1995 (Box 86, Folder 5-7)
      - Hospital Discharge, 1992-1993 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Hot Meals, 1992-1993 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Mental Health Linkage, 1992-1993 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Nutritional Services, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Social Services, 1992-1993 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Schedule and Instructions, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Technical Assistance, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Nutrition Services Proposal, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Nutritional Counseling Contract, 1992-1994 (Box 88, Folder 2-3)
    - The Off-Site Group Support Services Proposal, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Policies and Procedures Manual, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Program Committee, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Program Proposals, 1991-1992 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Public Funding Sources
      - General, 1992-1997 (Box 89, Folder 1-2)
      - AIDS Funding Report, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Renewal Instructions, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Requests for Proposals, 1990-1994, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 5-7)
    - Round I Summary, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - The Ryan White Comprehensive AIDS Resources Emergency Act of 1990, Information about (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Site Visit, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Spreadsheets, 1992-1993 (Box 90, Folder 4-5)
    - Staff Memoranda, 1996-1997 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Status of New Programs and Staffing, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Summary of Technical Assistance Provided, 1994-1995 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Supplement to Requests for Proposals, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Support Groups Services, 1992-1994 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Technical Assistance
      - Health Care Proposal, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - Ombudsman Contract, 1993-1994 (Box 90, Folder 12)
      - Requests proposal, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - United States ACTION/VISTA, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - United States Department of Health and Human Services
      - Alcohol, Drug Abuse and Mental Health Administration (ADAMHA), 1991-1993 (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, 1992 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - National Institutes of Health, research grants, 1988-1993 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Office of Community Services, 1992-1994 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Requests for applications, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Substance Abuse and Mental Health Services Administration (SAMHSA) linkage grant, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Utilization of community based services by people with AIDS, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - United States Health Resources and Services Administration
      - General, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - Site visit, 1992 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - VENDEX
      - General, 1992-1993 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Subcontractor questionnaire, 1992 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - III. B. Deaf AIDS Project, 1990-1997; 2 boxes
    The Deaf AIDS Project (DAP) began in 1987, independent of GMHC, when a group consisting of members of the deaf community, their supporters, and interpreters met to discuss the lack of AIDS education within the deaf community and homophobia within the environment of deaf services in New York City. English is a second language to many deaf Americans and the average deaf adult has a reading comprehension level between the third and eighth grade levels. Because of this, most of them did not know about AIDS. DAP looked to GMHC to provide a safe haven and to help form a permanent group to discuss these issues, but the two groups ran into a number of problems and were unable to form a permanent program until the early 1990s. In 1991, the DAP Staff Coordination Group was formed to create programs within GMHC that were focused on deaf clients. DAP established a Speakers Bureau to provide education about HIV/AIDS to deaf schools and organizations, implemented a TTY Hotline at GMHC, and produced HIV/AIDS videos and brochures for the deaf.
    Included in this series are mock-ups and notes on the HIV/AIDS brochure for the deaf community. The minutes of the DAP Staff Coordination Group describe the initial problems encountered by DAP and GMHC, the need for DAP, and other issues in the deaf community.
    - Advisory Committee, 1992-1995 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - American Sign Language, 1994-1995 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Brochure distribution, 1992-1997 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Committees, training information, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Deaf Accessibility Advisory Committee (DAAC), staff coordination group, 1995-1997 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Deaf Awareness Week, 1992-1995 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Deaf literature, 1991-1995 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Fundraising, 1992-1993 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - HIV/AIDS brochure
      - General, 1994-1996 (Box 92, Folder 11-12)
      - Focus group, 1995 (Box 93, Folder 1-2)
    - Memoranda, 1992-1994 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Schock, Brad, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Staff Coordination Group, 1990-1996 (Box 93, Folder 5-6)
    - Video proposal, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Volunteers
      - General, 1991-1995 (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Members and organizational charts, 1991-1993 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - III. C. Tuberculosis Education and Treatment Support Program, 1993-1997; 1 box
    The Tuberculosis Education and Treatment Support Program was developed in 1993 in response to the resurgence of tuberculosis (TB) in New York City. The program provided information about TB to clients, ongoing training about TB in social service settings and in the workplace, and sought to reduce the transmission of TB at GMHC facilities. Within the first year of the program HEPA filters were installed throughout the agency, tissues and face masks were made available on-site, TB posters and "cover your mouth" signs were posted in all reception areas, numerous on-site screenings for staff and clients were conducted, and a requirement was implemented for all new clients to provide documentation of their TB status.
    This subseries contains reports, memoranda, and correspondence of the Tuberculosis Education and Treatment Support Program. Included here are monthly reports and yearly reviews of the Program and minutes from the TB Working Group. All of these documents detail the steps taken by the TB program to reduce transmission of the disease within GMHC's community.
    - Budget narratives, 1996-1997 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Department of Health (New York City)
      - Budget variance reports, Fiscal year 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 93, Folder 12)
      - Bureau of Tuberculosis Control monthly reports, fiscal year 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Monthly reports, fiscal year 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Tuberculosis grant, fiscal year 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Documentation and redocumentation schedule, 1995-1997 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Outreach for Tuberculosis and Directly Observed Preventative Therapy (DOPT), 1995-1997 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Policy and procedures, 1995-1997 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Program review, 1994-1996 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Survey reports, 1994-1996 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Technical assistance reports, 1995-1996 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Training, 1993-1997 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Tuberculosis linkage agreements, 1994-1996 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Tuberculosis working group, 1993-1997 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Volunteers and the Volunteer Administration Liaison Group (VAL), 1994-1995 (Box 94, Folder 13)
- Series IV. Client Services, 1982-1999, n.d.; 24 boxes
  Client Services (known as Clinical Services until the mid 1980s) is the oldest department at GMHC, and developed out of the Buddy Program, which was initiated in 1982. The department managed the following programs:
  Case Management Crisis Intervention Services Financial Advocacy Group Support Intake Unit Nutrition and Recreation Services
  Each of these departments had a director or coordinator who reported to the head of Client Services.
  Only the records of the Crisis Intervention Services and a small amount of material from the Intake Unit and the Nutrition and Recreation Services were transferred from GMHC. Some material from the other Client Services departments may be found dispersed throughout the collection.
  Included are training manuals and handbooks, statistics on clients, and recreation program descriptions. There are three subseries, the Administrative Files, records of the Crisis Intervention Services, and Nutrition Assessment Forms. Audiovisual materials associate with these records can be found in Series XVI.B.1.
  - IV. A. Administrative Files, 1983-1994, n.d.; 9 boxes
    This subseries contains memoranda, minutes, correspondence, and reports produced by Client Services and its precursor, Clinical Services. Included are Buddy Support Program training manuals and Crisis Intervention Team handbooks which detail the roles of the Buddy and Crisis workers. Material from the Intake and Referral Department which includes manuals, statistics compiled by the Department of the numbers of clients admitted, memoranda, and client forms. Records of Recreation Services include descriptions of the program and the types of events sponsored, records of activities for 1987-1990, and client questionnaires. There are also minutes from Client Services staff meetings for 1983-1987 which reflect the growth of the department.
    - Ackerman Institute AIDS Project, 1987-1988 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Office memoranda, 1984-1987 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - AIDS & Adolescents Network, 1994 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - AIDS Fact-Finding Mission New York City Delegation to San Francisco, 1985 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - AIDS Institute
      - Monthly statistical reports
        - 1985-1988 (Box 95, Folder 5-10)
        - Miscellaneous, 1983-1984, 1987, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 11)
        - Referral and caseload, 1987-1991 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - AIDS surveillance update, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - AIDS training seminar proposal, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - AIDS Vigil in Central Park, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Audit, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Automation memoranda, 1985-1988 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Brochures, 1989, 1993-1994 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Buddies Nursing Consultation Program, 1983-1984, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Buddy Support Program
      - Team leaders, undated (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Training manual, 1983, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Budget request to City of New York, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Care Partners Group 7, 1984-1986 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Case Management
      - Intake Unit, 1989-1990 (Box 96, Folder 13)
      - Memoranda, 1988-1990, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 14-15)
    - Charting, 1983-1986 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Client demographic report, 1991 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Client information system, undated (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Client Services
      - Committee minutes, 1986-1990 (Box 96, Folder 19)
      - Directory brochure, 1992 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Management group, 1988-1989 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Planning committee, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Update, 1983-1985 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Waiting list, 1991-1992 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Clinicians Training Manual, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Community Based AIDS Organizations, undated (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Conference proceedings: Expanding and Integrating HIV Services, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Coordinator meeting minutes, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 97, Folder 10)